ZIAUL KARIM IFAZ

FULLSTACK WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT

- +880 1704403606
- Ohaka, Bangladesh
- https://ifaz.vercel.app
- https://github.com/ifazo
- www.linkedin.com/in/ifazo/

PROFILE

I'm Ifaz, fullstack web developer experienced in frontend frameworks like React, Angular, and Vue, as well as full-stack meta-frameworks like Next.js, Nuxt, and Analog. Also working with backend languages like Node.js, PHP, Go; and their framework like Express.js, Nest.js, Laravel. Devops tech like Docker, CI/CD. Also database management with MongoDB, PostgreSQL. Some projects are attached in my resume.

SKILLS

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript
- Bootstrap, tailwind
- React, Angular, Vue
- Next.js, Nuxt, Analog
- Node.js, express, nest.js
- PHP, Laravel
- Golang
- MongoDB, PostgreSQL, MySQL
- · Firebase, supabase, auth.js
- DevOps, Linux, Docker

EXPERIENCE

2023 - 2024 PROGRAMMING-HERO

fullstack web development intern

EDUCATION

2020 - 2024 COMILLA UNIVERSITY

• Bachelor in Computer Science

LANGUAGES

English: Fluent

Bangla: FluentHindi: Intermediate

• Urdu: Intermediate

WORK PROJECTS

Next project

Technologies: next.js (app), shadcn.ui, redux, auth, stripe, express, prisma

- Website: https://ifaz-next.vercel.app
- GitHub: https://github.com/ifazo/next-project

Next.js project

Technologies: next.js (page), tailwind, redux, next-auth, stripe, express, monsoose

- Website: https://ifaz-nextjs.vercel.app
- GitHub: https://github.com/ifazo/nextjs-project

React project

Technologies: react, tailwind, redux, firebase, stripe, node.js, mongodb

- Website: https://ifaz-react.vercel.app
- GitHub: https://github.com/ifazo/react-project

Angular project

Technologies: angular, tailwind, ngrx, firebase, stripe, bun, mongodb

- Website: https://ifaz-angular.vercel.app
- GitHub: https://github.com/ifazo/angular-project

Vue project

Technologies: vue, tailwind, pinia, firebase, stripe, deno, mongodb

- Website: https://ifaz-vue.vercel.app
- GitHub: https://github.com/ifazo/vue-project

ZIAUL KARIM IFAZ

FULLSTACK WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT

- +880 1704403606
- Ohaka, Bangladesh
- https://ifaz.vercel.app
- https://github.com/ifazo
- www.linkedin.com/in/ifazo

SKILLS

- JavaScript, TypeScript
- Node.js, Express, Nest.js
- PHP, Laravel
- Golang
- MongoDB, PostgreSQL
- DevOps, Linux, Docker
- Mongoose, Prisma, Drizzle
- · Stripe intergation
- · Multer file upload

EXPERIENCE

2023 - 2024 PROGRAMMING-HERO

• fullstack web development

intern

EDUCATION

2020 - 2024 COMILLA UNIVERSITY

• Bachelor in Computer Science

LANGUAGES

• English: Fluent

Bangla: Fluent

Hindi: Intermediate

· Urdu: Intermediate

PROFILE

I'm Ifaz, fullstack web developer experienced in frontend frameworks like React, Angular, and Vue, as well as full-stack meta-frameworks like Next.js, Nuxt, and Analog. Also working with backend languages like Node.js, PHP, Go; and their framework like Express.js, Nest.js, Laravel. Devops tech like Docker, CI/CD. Also database management with MongoDB, PostgreSQL. Some projects are attached in my resume.

WORK PROJECTS

Express prisma server

Technologies: express.js, prisma, mvc architecture, typescript, multer, stripe

- Postman: collection
- GitHub: https://github.com/ifazo/express-prisma-server

Express mongoose server

Technologies: express.js, mongoose, typescript, modular architechture, multer, stripe.

- Postman: collection
- GitHub: https://github.com/ifazo/express-mongoose-server

Nest.js server

Technologies: nest.js, prisma, typescript, multer, stripe

- Postman: collection
- GitHub: https://github.com/ifazo/nest-server

Laravel server

Technologies: php, laravel, multer, stripe

- Postman: collection
- GitHub: https://github.com/ifazo/laravel-server

Go server

Technologies: golang, multer, stripe

- Postman: collection
- GitHub: https://github.com/ifazo/go-server